I bet you've seen an infinite chocolate
trick before but have you seen one that
allows you to share the chocolate with a
friend start with this chocolate bar and
split it into these pieces as we've done
here there are actually two squares of
chocolate left inside you can split
those apart eat one yourself and share
the other with your favorite friend but
now to make sure that nobody knows that
you've done this you can take the
remaining pieces of the chocolate and
reorganize the triangular pieces like
this on either side and then take both
of the L-shaped pieces and drop them
down into place this way once you've
done this the full original chocolate
bar has been restored and no chocolate
is missing this triangular diagram is
based on the curry triangle which is a
dissection fallacy that allows you to
quote unquote prove that 60 59 and 58
are all equal